Hello everyone! Last week we saw how to buy your domains
from Cursor using Fewsats' MCP and
this week we are going to see how to buy anything from Cursor using
our Shopping MCP In order to solve,
first we need to set up two MCPs The first one is Fewsats',
that we saw already last week This is the one where our money is,
and it's able to to pay for offers, and the new one for this
week is Agora MCP This will provide us a shopping experience in
Cursor or any MCP client The
first thing that we'll do is, yesterday everyone was getting pictures of a Studio
Ghibli, so let's search for something like that So,
let's see what we have here, Spirited Away pencils,
Princess Mononoke, I like the Princess Mononoke,
so, nah, let's get the postcards Get me the postcards
What this will do is use the Agora MCP in order to get the
details of this purchase and get a postcard payment offer.
Once we have the payment offer, it will delegate into Fewsats MCP so
it can pay the offer. So,
it's asking for my user so I will give the user information now.
so now when the information is provided.
It will handle all the rest of the payment.
It will get the payment offers, and after that,
it will delegate into Fewsats, because Fewsats knows how to pay for one of
these offers. MCP has a small bug here that you can see,
but the agent is clever enough to fix it. I hope MCP developers can
fix it too. So, we can see it got the payment offers,
and then it called the pay offer,
and now we see that the payment status actually is need review.
Why is that? Because we do not completely trial the AI yet at Fewsats.
So, what we have is policies.
So, any API key that you use to pay can have different policies.
In my case, everything that an AI agent has to buy needs to be
approved by me, and as the MCP indicates,
you need to go to the website, to approve the request.
So, here you have the website, and if we refresh,
we will see that there is a new request,
and that the status is pending. So,
now I can go here, approve, and the payment went through.
And what is the cool thing about MCPs? Here,
we are using cursor, but MCPs can use,
be used for different, from very different clients.
For example, open AI today announced that they will support also MCP.
It's not yet available, but what we can do is,
we can now go to Claude, instead of cursor,
and say, hey, Claude,
can you check my latest orders?
And because the MCP is the same, it will be able to retrieve the
information. And
here you see, StudioGhibli,
quantity, status, paid. And that's it.
The cool thing about MCP clients is that now I'm buying it from cursor,
now I'm buying it from Claude. Next week I will be able to use
it also from ChatGPT, and hopefully very soon we will have someone write
an MCP client for mobile phone. So all these interfaces will
go to the same MCP.
And then, And you will have a seamless experience across all your devices.
That was everything from this week, and stay tuned for more.